<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Motorcycle</string>
    <string name="harleyMotorcycleBrand">Harley Davidson</string>
    <string name="iron883Title">Iron883</string>
    <string name="harleyIron883Description">The Iron 883 gets a good looking V-twin engine with a displacement of 883cc.
        The V-twin is air-cooled and brings along with it the classic Harley sound.
        The engine is mated to a five-speed manual transmission. The engine makes 49 hp and 54 lb-ft of torque.
        The Iron 883 opens the door to the Sportster line.
        It’s not the most powerful, but it offers a lot of style and substance for the money. The bike has a starting price of $8,999.</string>


    <string name="harleyFXDR114Title">FXDR114</string>
    <string name="harleyFXDR114Description">The FXDR 114 has the Milwaukee-Eight 114 engine.
        It’s an air-cooled V-twin that has a displacement of 1,868cc. The 114 engine is mated to a six-speed manual transmission
        and it makes 119 lb-ft of torque.
        The FXDR 114is the kind of bike you get if you love the Harley-Davidson brand but you want
        something with some modern styling and a look completely different than HD’s other bikes.
        The FXDR 114 is a unique cruiser and unlike other Softail machines. The company has a price tag of $18,999 on it.</string>


    <string name="bmwMotorcycleBrand">BMW</string>
    <string name="bmwR1250RTitle">R1250R</string>
    <string name="bmwR1250RDescription">The model features a 1,254cc twin-cylinder boxer engine that makes 136 hp and 105
        lb-ft of torque. It’s an engine design that BMW uses in several motorcycles in its lineup.
        This engine has enough power around town, country road, and highway duties, and its boxer design gives you the true BMW experience.
        The R 1250 R is at home on the open road, but it’s also a fantastic urban machine. The motorcycle is sporty looking and comfortable, and it offers a unique naked roadster riding experience.
        This makes the $14,995 price tag reasonable.</string>

</resources>